Mr. Sun,
what happened to my dad?
Don't worry too much.
They just took your dad away
for questioning.
Do I really have to leave?
The creditors
are after you now
and we have to take you
to a safe place right away.
But I have my own plans.
I've got the
prep school admission letter.
I wanna study abroad as my mom
wished.
Ye,
your father's assets
have been frozen.
It'll be tough to get a visa.
You have no other relatives
here in Beijing.
I need to focus fully on
your father's case.
I can't rest easy
if you stay in Beijing.
Where are we going now?
Zhazhating.
We'll go to your aunt's.
Zhazhating?
Step aside!
Freeze!
- Stop!
- Make way!
Step away!
Don't move!
Excuse me!
Wu Laoer!
Coming through!
Move!
Wu Laoer!
Wu!
What's going on?
Catch the thief!
Wu Laoer stole
Mr. Zhu's phone.
What happened?
How dare he!
Mr. Zhu's phone got stolen.
Mr. Zhu?
Was it Wu Laoer?
Exactly.
Wu,
don't forget to pick up your cousin.
Got it.
Follow me, Wu.
- Take care.
- Hurry!
Stay safe!
Wu Laoer!
Look who it is!
Steal things again!
Never stays out of trouble.
Let's split up!
- Okay.
- Got it.
Wu Laoer!
Hurry up! Kyle!
What's wrong?
What the hell?
The GPS seems off.
[OMG.]
[Shamates...]
You!
Bastard!
Where's the phone?
What phone?
Don't play dumb.
The road is covered with cameras.
How dare you steal the teacher's phone?
Huh?
Wait, what are you talking about?
Wu! Wait!
I just stole a phone.
No need to do that.
Give it to me!
You're pinning me down.
How can I get it out?
What are you doing?
The phone!
Kyle!
Big G!
Take it.
I...
Fuck off!
A Beijing plate car.
Looks really fancy.
Wu.
Is that...
our cousin's car?
Ye,
I know that
the surroundings and locals here
are a bit different
from what you expected.
But there are relatives looking after you here.
I've told them over and over again
to keep you safe at all costs.
It's way more than just a little different.
I just saw three people picking on one
and acting shamelessly everywhere.
Ye,
it's none of your business.
Just take it easy.
I don't care.
What's this?
Hey beauty.
Good to see you.
I'm
Kyle Hao,
the richest man in Zhazhating.
What's wrong with you?
You're from Beijing, right?
None of your business.
Buddy.
You three
locals?
Yep.
What's up?
How can I
get to Xuan Island?
Xuan...
Xuan Island?
- Nah...
- Eh...
100 yuan
as your reward.
100 yuan?
Okay, 100 yuan for each of you.
No.
Enough?
No need to pay.
It's opposite the lighthouse.
You'll see a row of red houses.
Go straight along this road
about one kilometer to the main road,
turn left twice at the roundabout
and follow the small path till the end.
What a winding route!
No wonder the GPS got confused.
Take this.
Thank you.
You city folks are really generous.
Return it.
They got into the car.
Such a generous spender!
Mr. Sun,
is this what you call
honest folk?
In a small town,
money talks
and all issues will get sorted.
Mr. Zhu.
Look at your hair!
Such weird colors!
Do you even look like students?
Ouch, that hurts.
Where's Wu Laoer?
Don't worry. We found him.
You can trust Wu.
It's here.
Check if anything's wrong.
Seems all fine.
But what's that smell?
If everything's fine,
we'll leave.
You two head back first.
Xing Wu,
come with me.
I need a word with you.
You two take the shortcut
to tell my mom
our cousin will arrive soon.
Okay.
South wind first, good fortune all the way.
See you.
West wind.
Fangfang,
Your makeup
looks really fancy today.
Just so-so.
Got any big plans?
My niece is coming
from Beijing soon.
Fangfang,
I've heard your niece
will give you 50,000 yuan.
That's a huge sum.
You'll be well-off then.
Enough to pay off all debts.
Who spread that gossip?
Don't you remember?
You told me
when you dried my hair
last time in person.
You sure have a bad memory.
Fine.
Guess I forgot.
It's not about money.
We're family after all.
Taking care of her
is only natural.
I don't need payment.
Fangfang,
you've got relatives in the capital?
Never heard you mention it.
We haven't kept in touch much.
She's my sister's daughter.
Their family runs
a big business.
Really prosperous.
But my sister passed away
at an early age.
It happened a couple of years before.
My brother-in-law
still acknowledges our kinship.
I've already
talked to him.
In the future,
he must come to invest
and develop Zhazhating
into a resort town.
New buildings will be built too.
I'll get each of you
an apartment.
Really?
Thanks a lot.
I'll hold you to that.
Okay.
Someone's calling.
Pick up first.
Okay.
Hello.
Calm down.
I told you.
Once the God of Wealth arrives,
I'll transfer the money right away.
Hello?
Jesus!
How stubborn you are!
You've been persuading me into this
for two years.
You are
my student after all.
I just wanna talk with you.
Just have a heart-to-heart chat.
Nothing wrong with it.
I heard that
you've been fixing phones at Shunyi
for almost two years.
Are you really hooked on this job?
You have no intention of going back to school
and take college entrance exams?
How do you know that
going back guarantees a good university?
I'm fine living like this now.
As your teacher,
I know you well.
You just feel
your mom struggles alone.
She pays for your schooling,
settles family debts
and looks after
your grandma.
Life is tough for her.
You wanna share her burden.
But Xing Wu,
think it through rationally.
Resuming your studies right now
and striving for a good college
are the best reward
you can give your mother.
Listen.
You used to be
an outstanding student.
Remember the paper plane contest
in Zhazhating.
Your plane flew the highest
and farthest.
Save it.
It's just folding paper planes.
Drop it.
What about the
model aircraft competition?
You were also the champion.
Wu Laoer was also your junior.
Two years after leaving school
and he still mucks around.
Don't mention him.
You two are totally different.
Everyone walks their own path.
Just like in Zhazhating,
across one alley, accents change;
across one ridge, customs range.
In my
opinion,
you are a promising talent.
Your mom had no choice
but to suspend your schooling.
Let bygones be bygones.
Two years have passed.
What's there to linger on?
Still quarrel with your wife
lately?
He Xiaolian and I...
We're talking about you.
Why drag me into this?
Xing Wu,
I've talked to you
so many times.
Please think carefully.
Finished?
Okay.
Goodbye, Mr. Zhu.
Take your time to consider.
Call me once you make up your mind.
Auntie Fang.
Cou...
Auntie Fang,
the cousin has arrived.
Xing Wu asked me to inform you.
My son,
what happened to your hair?
Who did it for you?
It's me.
I got new
hair dye.
They two dropped out of school.
I just tried it out on them.
But it looks really ugly!
Standing there and
they look like traffic lights.
Please dye it back right away.
Dye it back right away!
Fine.
They look like hooligans!
Okay.
Kyle, Big G,
tell Liu Nian to
to light firecrackers to welcome her!
Okay!
OMG.
What a weird hairstyle!
Take my bag please.
I'm gonna greet my God of Wealth.
Let's go together.
Come on!
I'll take it.
Okay.
She's coming!
Really?
Light the firecrackers!
OMG!
So lively!
Welcome!
Nice to meet you.
Ye's aunt?
Yes.
Li Lanfang?
Yes, it's me.
We spoke on the phone.
Secretary Sun Hai?
It's me.
Good to see you.
She's Ye.
Okay.
Ye!
Finally get to see you!
Give me a hug.
So stylish!
Truly a city girl!
You've grown so tall!
Remember me?
You visited here when you were a kid.
Okay, fine.
You're here now!
Trust me.
I, as your aunt,
will take good care of you.
Neighbors,
this is my niece
from Beijing,
Qing Ye.
Bravo!
Welcome!
Hope all of you
look after her!
Sure. No problem!
Thank you all!
Liu Nian,
fetch the luggage.
That's all!
Thanks.
Thank you.
Brilliant!
Let's go back home.
Let's go inside.
I need a word with Sun.
Fine. Just go.
We'll head in first.
Hurry up, Liu Nian!
Okay!
Mr. Sun,
you've worked for my dad for so many years.
Please clear his name.
I'll spare no effort
to do that.
Don't worry.
Ye,
take care of yourself.
Call me
whenever you want to.
Bye.
Ye,
this is Xuan Island.
Welcome to Xuan Island.
This is my barbershop.
It looks messy
but well-organized actually.
This is my apprentice, Liu Nian.
Nice to meet you.
Go sweep up the firecracker scraps
or the neighbors may blame us.
Okay.
Thank you.
30,000 yuan?
We agreed on 50,000 yuan!
This is the initial payment.
Small as the
place is,
it has all
facilities.
The deal was 50,000 yuan,
including board and lodging.
Is something wrong?
I won't stay long.
Compared to a hotel,
30,000 yuan is at least as much,
if not more.
The rest
will be paid
before I leave.
Fine.
Just stay here.
We're family,
aren't we?
I promise
I'll make you
feel at home.
This is my son,
Xing Wu.
This is your cousin from Beijing,
Qing Ye.
I'm going next door.
Ugh...
Show Qing Ye around
later.
I'm busy.
Fine.
I'll show you your room
upstairs.
Jesus...
How many things are there
in your luggage?
It's so heavy!
Come here.
This way.
My son fixes phones
and gadgets right here.
You can
sleep here.
Here?
Is this your son's room?
Of course.
He barely stays home,
always out running errands.
It's a nice spot for you.
Facing the sea, spring blossoms.
You take this bed
and he sleeps over there.
If you feel awkward,
I can hang a curtain.
If that still
doesn't work,
I can put up a partition board.
Is that okay?
Any other options?
Have a look
at my room.
Small
but functional,
cozy and well arranged.
Take a look.
You can live here.
Just tidy it up a bit.
So...
which one?
OMG...
Don't be scared.
It's alright.
Liu Nian
uses it to practice.
Which one do you prefer?
[Fang, we're waiting for you.]
[Come on!]
Coming.
How about you
take some time to think it over?
I'll go play mahjong first.
I'll let Wu
show you around later.
Call him if you need anything.
Rub, rub the head,
no need to fear.
What's your problem?
Why the long face?
Why are you so cold to her?
As kids,
you two played together .
You went clam digging. Remember?
She is such a poor girl.
Her mom passed away years ago.
I think
her father wouldn't
send her here
without encounter of real problem.
Lost contact for years
and she's here now because of a problem.
My sister treated me well.
She took me in
and loved me
like her own
sister.
She privately
gave me money
when I was pregnant.
Be welcoming!
She's our honored guest.
Ye,
you can turn to Liu Nian
if Wu
is unavailable.
Wu!
Where's the restroom?
Outside.
It's public one.
Public?
Something wrong?
By the way,
this is my grandma's room.
She's resting.
Don't go in unless you have to.
Don't mess with things downstairs.
Here's my number.
I've got things to do.
Call me if you need me.
Mom...
Sweetie, you're awake.
Mom,
I just had a nightmare.
I'm so scared.
My babe,
it was just a dream.
What did you dream about?
Tell me.
I dreamed of a place
called Zhazhating
where I met
my aunt, Li Lanfang,
her son, Xing Wu,
along with
his weird-looking friends.
They had their hair dyed
in all sorts of colors
and acted really rudely.
I don't like them at all.
Don't be afraid.
It's just a dream.
Mom?
Why are you here?
Had a nightmare?
No, I don't.
Good to hear that.
What's up?
Distinguished guest,
my mom asks you for dinner.
I got it.
Ye,
come and have dinner.
Auntie,
is the light
always dim?
Yep.
Do you ask your grandma?
Does she wanna eat here
or in her room?
She says she's not hungry.
His grandma has bad legs.
I cooked
three dishes specially
to welcome you.
The soup will be ready
in a minute.
Ye,
have some meat first.
Thanks.
I don't eat meat in the evening.
No meat?
You're still growing up.
You need meat!
Too much fat
harms health.
So have seafood.
Clams won't make you fat.
Have it.
As an old saying goes,
seafood cooked
with lard
tastes amazing!
Delicious!
I don't eat lard.
Suit yourself.
Wu,
get her
a bowl of noodles.
No need.
I'm not hungry
I came down
to show you this
accommodation service contract.
Stay in a hotel if you have money.
Such a childish contract
means nothing here.
What's wrong with the contract?
Ye has given the money.
Signing a contract
is just routine.
Okay. I'll sign.
You city folks
really stick to rules.
One more thing.
I won't
pay the balance
if my
personal safety
gets threatened
during my stay here.
Don't worry.
Nothing like that
will happen.
I hope so.
Fine.
Two copies in total.
Keep one for yourself.
Okay.
I'm heading upstairs
Sure you won't eat anything?
I'm not hungry.
Our life is tough enough.
Why do we take on such a demanding guest?
Before doing that,
could you please figure out
how to live life?
Our hardship
is all
because of
your unreliable father,
Xing Guodong.
He gambled away
my shop.
Or would I scrape every penny
at the cost of
your tuition and
your grandmother's medical bills?
Do you think
fixing gadgets
can pay off such huge debts?
Okay. Enough.
It's not enough!
I'm not finished!
Your grandma has trouble getting around now
and has epilepsy.
Going to the hospital
also needs money.
Let me tell you!
If it weren't for
30,000 yuan from Qing Ye today,
from now on, you, me, your grandma,
we'd all be in deep trouble
with those debt collectors.
So,
she's our savior right now.
We have to treat her like royalty.
I know.
For the sake of this family,
you have had a really hard time.
As a mother,
I feel sorry for you.
I don't want you to be so tired.
Let's pay off the debt first.
Then, work a little harder,
and maybe you
can go back to school.
I believe with your ability,
you can definitely be admitted
to a good university.
Studying is the right path.
Who said I wanted to go to university?
I can support this family.
Then, could we consider this money as a loan?
When we have money in the future,
we pay her back, okay?
Do you know, she,
for our family,
is like a handful of useless tiles
that suddenly drew a winning hand.
Li Lanfang,
how could you compare everything
to playing mahjong?
My son,
in life,
you need something to hold onto.
You can't overthink
every single thing.
Take myself, for example.
In my whole life,
I've been paying off your dad's debt.
And you,
you're just paying my debt.
I went through a lot,
giving birth to you.
Actually, I'm not hungry.
Play mahjong again?
Please allow me.
Okay?
Fine. Just go.
Thank you.
Remember to clean up
all this stuff, okay?
[Wu,]
[Wu.]
- [Grandma.]
- [Come in.]
[Be careful.]
[I know]
[both you and your mother have it hard.]
[Don't be angry with her.]
[Just let her go.]
[When she's playing mahjong,]
[she's actually a bit happier.]
Got it, grandma.
I'll go get you some food.
I'm not hungry.
Eating too much late isn't good for digestion.
Don't you like
sea urchin with steamed egg?
When I get paid,
I'll buy it for you.
My grandson is so thoughtful.
What's wrong?
Must be a power outage.
I'll go check, grandma.
I was in such a hurry to leave this time.
I didn't bring anything with me.
I left my computer at school.
[Okay, I'll send it to you tomorrow.]
You need to send it express.
I need it for course registration.
[Okay, don't worry.]
[Qing Ye,]
[how long do you plan on staying over there?]
I've made an estimate...
You see,
course registration,
and waiting for my visa.
Oh, Leling,
the proof of assets I need,
did you get it ready for me?
[Almost.]
[I asked my mom to help with the funds.]
[It should be done by next week.]
That's great.
Then I'm guessing about a month,
and I can
get out of
this crappy place.
Check this out.
[Qing Ye,]
[Why don't you turn on the lights?]
Can you believe it?
The power's out here.
[Power out?]
[How could it be?]
[Qing Ye,]
[do you really go on a reality show like "X-change"?]
Let me tell you.
It's insane.
Forget it.
I don't wanna talk about it.
[Don't you have a cousin there?]
[What about him?]
He?
I don't even know where to start.
His hair
is like not quite blonde, not quite silver,
and he has a bad temper.
He's exactly
the kind of "bleached-hair punk" you'd imagine.
Like a little thug.
[Qing Ye,]
[there's a ghost behind you.]
Jesus.
How come you can walk,
without making a sound?
No sound is perfect.
It lets me hear you trash-talking people behind their backs.
I'll hang up the video.
Stay in the dark.
Do you smell it?
Why is it so stinging?
Haven't you used mosquito coils before?
Don't you have an electric mosquito repellent?
The odorless, non-toxic kind?
This area is known for its sea mosquitoes.
Mosquito coils work the best.
By the way,
a friendly tip for you.
These mosquitoes
can bite a pig to death.
How many times have you been bitten?
Who are you calling a pig?
It seems like my assessment of you
wasn't complete enough.
I'll add two more.
Sarcastic,
and pretentious.
Also,
talk to me less from now on.
I'm a clean freak.
What now?
Another blackout?
What are you doing?
You said it was too dark.
So I wanna get you a brighter bulb.
Don't just sit there.
The bulb.
Give it to me.
Can't you get it yourself?
You don't have to look at me like that.
At most one month later,
I'll be out of here
for further study abroad.
As for me,
I'll just treat this as a summer vacation here.
During this time,
you have the right to be annoyed, to dislike me,
and not to stand me.
But I won't change.
That's just how it is between party A and party B.
We tolerate each other for one month,
and then it's over.
One month at most.
Leave as soon as you can.
Never see each other again.
That's also what I'm thinking.
Wait a minute.
There are so many sea mosquitoes here.
Do you have any special mosquito repellent
or even some floral water lotion?
This is all I've got.
Does that work?
I don't like the smell.
Don't be so picky unless you want scars from scratching.
Suit yourself.
Hold on a sec.
Where's the bathroom?
Here we are.
Right here.
This is...the bathroom?
Yep.
Public bathroom.
Wait.
How can you share a shower
with your neighbors?
In Zhazhating,
this is what we've got.
Right here.
Why is it so smelly?
That's all rusted.
The floor is so dirty.
It's even bulk shampoo!
How can I take a shower with these?
Water heater.
Showerhead.
Why can't you shower?
In Zhazhating,
this is what we've got.
What about the door?
How can I lock this door?
What?
There's even a hole here.
It's old and worn out.
Broken.
Are you kidding me?
What if someone comes by,
crouches down, and sees me showering?
On such a hot day,
nobody's going out of their way
to peek at you showering.
Just pull that curtain
and you're fine.
This is what we've got in Zhazhating.
The shampoo...
Is there any other shampoo?
Yes.
Wait a bit.
Body wash?
Soup.
I can't stand using soap.
Alright.
Whatever conditions you have,
speak all out at once.
Shampoo.
I need silicone‑free shampoo,
and niacinamide face wash.
For toothpaste, I'd like...
Forget it.
It's only a month anyway.
I'll suck it up.
Xing Wu!
Ugh... I...
What's wrong?
Th‑there…there are bugs!
Bugs?
So many bugs!
You see them?
There are no bugs.
There are lots!
You mean this?
Don't! Don't! Stay away!